

ENRIQUE DONAIRE

FIlm and Vídeo Editor

+34 662146383

www.linkedin.com/in/enrique-andres-donaire-45089a295

https://enriquedonaire.github.io/Portfolio-AV

PROFILE

Highly creative filmmaker gaduated of Digital Cinema & Video editor, with over 5 years of experience making a variety of shortfilms and advertising videos for diverses freelance companies and independent directors. Strong Passion for creating short films with great stories, but also have a knack for creating commercial productions and documentaries Knowledge of latest cameras, video and audio equipament and editing software. Enjoys working with a variety of scripts, actors and crew members at many different experience levels. in love with visual storytelling, from drawing to film.

EXPERIENCE

Videographer and Video editing | Freelance

09/2021-07/2023 | Granada - Spain

- Filmed and directed +3 advertising reels for different clients.
- Managed at least over 10 people of different department including art and photography.
- All the photographies on set was taken under my team supervision
- Lead post-production of 3 short films in Spain and Argentina.

Cinema Director & Producer | Freelance

03/2021-08/2021 | Granada - Spain

- Produced, filmed and directed +4 short film and +5 advertising reels for different clients.
- Coordinated the work of groups of +10 people with different specific tasks.
- Reviewed recorded images and sounds to develop
- Instructing for post production to +5 personal of the film.
- Overhauled +2 teamwork for the digital post-production of +4 shortfilms.

Videographer and Editor | Banana Marketing - Intern

09/2020-02/2021 | Granada - Spain

- Edited more than 15 advertising videos and photography weekly
- Helped on shooting days with a third camera and edited and delivered this material to the different socials medias platforms.
- · Corporate Videos.

Photographer | La Casa de Humberto

2015-2017 | San Telmo - Buenos Aires

- Photograprhy and Videos
- Branding.
- · Short films.

Creative & Photographer | UN-NO-LUGAR

2010 -2012 | Cordoba - Argentina

- Live Streaming of the Pixelation art festival (2010)
- Diffusion of Emerging Art on social networks and in cultural centers (Spain-Córdoba Museum of Art and Culture)
- Murals in Anamorphism X-DISTANTE, in the Genaro Pérez Córdoba Museum - Argentina

EXPERIENCE

Videographer and Editor | Monos con Alma

2006 - 2009 | La Rioja - Argentina

- Advertising short films
- Branding
- Social Media Audiovisuals service.
- Live Video Streaming

EDUCATION

Photography and Photoshop | Monos con Alma Productions

03/2007-09/2009 | La Rioja- Argentina

- Completed 2 years
- Foundation of Photography
- Workshop: Photoshop photo editing.
- Worked on set of 3 short films as Camera assistant and DOP

Camera & Digital Production | Grenade School Art

10/2019-10/2020 | Granada - Spain

- Experienced working in different fields of the film industry.
- Managed film set safety and precautions.
- Tech stack: Davinci Resolve, Adobe Premier, After Effects, Pro Tools.

Full-Stack JavaScript Developer | Ironhack

05/2021-08/2021 | SPAIN - REMOTE

Technical knowledge about

- Learned +10 programming languages...
- Launched +10 Web Dev projects and +3 Full Apps.
- Tech stack: React JS, Nodejs, Expressjs, MongoDB, Mongoose, HTML, CSS, JSX, REST API, Javascript.

LANGUAGES

- Spanish Native
- English C1
- Italian B2

HARD SKILLS SOFT SKILLS

Adobe Premiere Pro
Davinci Resolve Studio
Pro Tools Avid
After Ef fects / Fusion
effects
Fairligth Audio
Photoshop
Lightroom
Adobe Illustrator
Audacity
JavasCript

Storytelling Communication Creativity Teamwork Team Motivator Adaptable Efficient Innovative Details Watcher Detail Observer Patient